Hello friends, today I will tell you in this video
that when you have a tree here, then
your sister, are your bangles made
or not, the answer is that the bank calls and says that
our money should be returned to you and whether it happened to you
or not, we have nothing to do with it, they
return your money,
you know
how much they take regarding your credit card, when
that word happens, there is an increase in customers,
when it is a platform, it
is decided in two ways, there is an increase in customers in the first page,
Aishwarya RBI guidelines
and romantic decrease, when you have
no involvement in the fraud that has happened, it is from the
bank's necklace, it is the bank's deficiency,
it happened because of the bank's
employees or they have done
this fraud with you in collusion,
where you have nothing to do with it, you do not do any
OTP, they have put a ban on you, please
bank has not sent you anything from this life,
I have not sent you anything,
cheers to me, if you do not add any other TP password seed number, then
I have no responsibility in it,
now we will leave from here  In time, the
growth of the tortoise will be sidelined because
what happens in this case is that the customer has shared the OTP password or
cigarette number
with four people due to which money gets deducted from his account,
so here you will be fully
responsible because the
problem here has happened due to your mistake
and this responsibility will continue till the time this is the public's
bank, see that my pattern lock is done,
I made a mistake and this is
over, so till the card is
not blocked, whatever
money gets deducted from your account, that is all your
responsibility, you will have to decide and
one point was happening in this case that when it is
not your fault, it is not the bank's
fault, the third party has also done some fraud
that I have deducted money from your work, they have done
some fraud through the website, then
in that case, or if you get a
message, then do
not sit on that message, you have to go and inform the bank as soon as possible to
United Bank, win
thrilling draw with free working S, you do not
tell that you had merged in four to seven days  The
default was that, what will happen
if your PAT limit is up to 5 lakhs, then
people with PAT limit up to 5 lakhs will have to pay Rs. 10000,
if your limit is
more than 5 lakhs, then its amount
will increase to Rs. 25000, so now you must have understood
that if, where it is not your fault,
you have not shared it with others, then the
bank will call you, send a legal notice, do
anything, you will clearly reply to it in Britain, you will make
friendship, answer on the call and say that
I have not done anything to anyone, then I have
no responsibility, you should
stop torturing me every day, so
if you liked the video, then
like it, share it and
definitely tell me your opinion by commenting, thank you.